Adventure has a new name.
Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure is a family,
animation, romance film directed by Darrell Rooney.
Lady and Tramp's mischievous pup, Scamp, gets fed up with rules and restrictions
imposed on him by life in a family, and longs for a wild and free lifestyle.
He runs away from home and into the streets where he joins a pack of stray dogs known as the "Junkyard Dogs."
Buster, the pack's leader, takes an instant disliking to the "house-dog" and considers him a rival.
Angel, a junkyard pup Scamp's age, longs for the safety and comfort of
life in a family and the two become instant companions.
Will Scamp choose the wild and free life of a stray or
the unconditional love of his family?
Scamp (speaking) (voice), played by Scott Wolf.
Angel (speaking) (voice), played by Alyssa Milano.
Buster (speaking) (voice), played by Chazz Palminteri.
Tramp / Jock / Trusty / Dogcatcher (voice), played by Jeff Bennett.
Lady (voice), played by Jodi Benson.
Mooch (voice), played by Bill Fagerbakke.
Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure is a 2001 American animated direct-to-video musical romantic comedy film produced by
Walt Disney Television Animation, and the sequel to Disney's 1955 animated feature film Lady and the Tramp.
The film was directed by Darrell Rooney and Jeannine Roussel,
with a screenplay by Bill Motz and Bob Roth.
It stars Scott Wolf as Lady and Tramp's son Scamp,
who desires to become a wild dog.
In the film, Scamp runs away from his home and joins a gang of stray dogs called the
Junkyard Dogs, where he falls in love with one of the gang's members, Angel.
Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure was released on
February 27, 2001, to mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of cartoon, sequel,
initiation, cartoon dog, dogcatcher.
The tone is emotional.